Donald F. Carmony papers, 1949-1984 C4
Indiana University Archives
- Indiana University, 1955-1984
  - IU committees, 1957-1982; undated
    - Historic New Harmony Institute, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Heritage Committee: (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1982 (Box 4)
      - Historic Preservation Subcommittee, 1966-1979; undated (Box 4)
      - Hoosier Heritage Hall Committee, 1969-1981 (Box 4)
      - Meeting minutes, 1976-1982 (Box 4)
    - IU Sesquicentennial Committee (Box 4)
      - 1964-1968 (Box 4)
      - 1969-1970, undated (Box 4)
      - Film materials, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
      - Meeting minutes, 1964-1970; undated (Box 4)
      - Planning manual, 1969 (Box 4)
    - Intergroup Relations Committee – Workshop, 1954-1956 (Box 4)
    - Kinsey Award Committee: (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 4)
      - Meeting minutes, 1980 (Box 4)
    - Lilly Program in American History (Box 4)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 4)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 4)
      - Items re program renewal, 1961-1963 (Box 4)
    - Lilly Library Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
    - Professional Status of Librarians Committee: (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1973; undated (Box 4)
      - Final Report, 1970 (Box 4)
      - Librarian job descriptions, 1970 (Box 4)
      - Majority and minority report materials, 1970; undated (Box 4)
      - Meeting minutes, 1969-1971; undated (Box 4)
      - Preliminary reports, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
      - Relevant articles and publications, 1957-1972 (Box 4)
      - Study C, 1971 (Box 4)
      - Protection of Human Subjects Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
    - University Museum Committee, 1962-1981 (Box 4)
  - IU subject files, 1964-1980; undated
    - Audio-Visual Center - Film on Canal Transportation, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Buley memorial, 1964­1978; undated (Box 4)
    - Commencement speech given by Dean H.T. Briscoe, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Dow Chemical incident and other protests, 1964-1968 (Box 4)
      (2 folders)
    - Focus: The Environment, 1970-1971; undated (Box 4)
    - Hurt, John E. Papers, 1975-1978 (Box 4)
    - IU Press, 1969; undated (Box 4)
    - Madden, Ray J. Papers, 1968-1970 (Box 4)
    - News releases, 1966-1982 (Box 4)
    - Oral History Research Program, 1968 (Box 4)
    - Retirement - Re. IMH, New Harmony Commission, preparation for full retirement, 1968-1980 (Box 4)
- Outside organizations, 1956-1981; undated
  - Adult Education Association, 1957-1961; undated (Box 4)
    - Bulletins, memos and newsletters (Box 4)
      - 1957-1959 (Box 4)
      - 1960, undated (Box 4)
    - Conferences, meeting minutes and reports, 1959-1961 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 5)
    - Defining the Role of a National Organization – A study, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Financial reports, membership and subscriptions, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - University of Illinois Division of University Extension – Newsletter, 1960 (Box 5)
  - American Association of State and Local History, 1962-1977; undated
    - Administrative materials (Box 5)
      - 1964-1971 (Box 5)
      - 1972-1975, undated (Box 5)
    - Award nominations (Box 5)
      - 1966 (Box 5)
      - 1967 (Box 5)
      - 1968-1971 (Box 5)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
      - 1962 (Box 5)
      - 1963 (Box 5)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 5)
      - 1966 (Box 5)
      - 1967 (Box 5)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 5)
      - 1970-1973 (Box 5)
      - 1974-1977 (Box 5)
    - Roster of Awards of Merit, 1972; 1975 (Box 5)
  - Bloomington Bicentennial Commission, 1975-1976; undated
    - Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976; undated (Box 5)
    - Honey School project, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Pending, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
    - Seminary Park, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Commission on Higher Education, 1973-1974
    - Correspondence and reports, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Hoosier Historical Tours, 1964-1967; undated
    - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1964-1966; undated (Box 5)
  - Indiana History Committee, 1959-1961
    - Meeting minutes and memoranda, 1959-1961 (Box 5)
  - Indiana History Panel / Indiana Higher Education Telecommunication System, 1972-1976; undated
    - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 5)
    - Meeting minutes and related material, 1972-1975; undated (Box 5)
    - Proposals, 1974 (Box 5)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1959-1962
    - Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 5)
    - Meetings and conferences, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - Memoranda, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - Newsletters-Indiana region, 1961 (Box 5)
  - NDEA, 1966-1967
    - Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - National University Extension Association, 1959-1960
    - Directors, Committees, Delegates, and Special Appointees, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - Subcommittee on Liberal Education, 1959 (Box 5)
  - New Harmony Commission, 1968-1981; undated (Box 6)
    - Articles and clippings, 1973; 1976; undated (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 6)
    - Meeting minutes and memoranda, 1973-1978 (Box 6)
    - Memorabilia Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 6)
    - New Harmony Film (Box 6)
      - 1968-1972, undated (Box 6)
      - -Scripts, 1970 (Box 6)
    - New Harmony Opera, 1973; undated (Box 6)
    - Owen, Robert, Bicentennial Celebration, 1969-1971; undated (Box 6)
  - State Social Studies Curriculum Revision Committee, 1956-1964; undated
    - Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 6)
    - Meeting minutes and reports, 1956-1964; undated (Box 6)
- Subject files, 1953-1983; undated
  - Awards and clippings, 1969-1983 (Box 6)
  - Bibliographies, 1953; undated (Box 6)
  - Campus Club, 1956 (Box 6)
  - Cloud, Joseph D., 1981 (Box 6)
  - Drafts and draft commentary, 1958; 1983 (Box 6)
  - Film on Pioneer Mill, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Hershey Library, 1951-1971 (Box 6)
  - Historic Madison and Southern Indiana river trails, 1971-1981 (Box 6)
  - Recommendations, 1951-1984 (Box 6)
    [Restricted]
- Great Books, 1940s-1973; undated
  - Clinics, 1951-1954
    - October 11-13, 1951 (Box 6)
    - August 28-30, 1952 (Box 6)
    - Receipts for clinics, 1952; 1953 (Box 6)
    - August 10-12, 1953 (Box 6)
    - 1954 (Box 6)
  - Alphabetical files, 1940s-1973; undated
    - Adolfson, L.H., 1950 (Box 6)
    - Annual Report, 1953-1954 (Box 6)
    - Barden, John P., 1947; 1952 (Box 6)
    - Bartley, Ross, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Bower, Elizabeth, 1951 (Box 6)
    - Brigham, Harold, 1951-1955 (Box 6)
    - Cavanaugh, John J., 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - Clark, Dr. William E., 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - Dennis, Richard, 1951-1954 (Box 6)
    - Efroymson, C.W., 1951 (Box 6)
    - French, Pauline, 1954-1955 (Box 6)
    - Goodrich, Pierre E. (Box 6)
      - 1949-1952 (Box 6)
      - 1953-1973 (Box 6)
    - Holton, James T., 1952-1954 (Box 6)
    - Indiana State Committee and Steering and Planning Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
    - Levy, Nathan, 1951 (Box 6)
    - Mailing list roster, 1952-1954; undated (Box 6)
    - Mangold, Dr. Hans, 1955 (Box 6)
    - Materials, ca. 1940s-1950s (Box 6)
    - Memorandums, 1950-1952 (Box 6)
      (Reports – Background of Great Books)
    - News Letter, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Pattullo, E.L., 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Perguson, Mr. Dee, 1952-1955 (Box 6)
    - Publicity, 1950-1955 (Box 6)
    - Reading lists, 1952-1953; undated (Box 6)
    - Reports and Memorandums, 1951-1953 (Box 6)
    - Questionnaires (Box 6)
      - Clinic questionnaire, 1953 (Box 6)
      - Supply form letters, 1951-1953 (Box 6)
      - Ten year report, 1955 (Box 6)
      - Replies to (Box 6)
        - 1951 (Box 6)
        - 1952 (Box 7)
        - 1953 (Box 7)
        - 1954 (Box 7)
    - Schacht, Dr. Robert H., 1952 (Box 7)
    - Stencils and ditos, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Strubbe, Charles, 1950-1952 (Box 7)
    - Trippet, Byron K., 1950-1955 (Box 7)
    - Wells, Herman B, 1950-1952 (Box 7)
  - City files, 1947-1956
    - Akron, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Anderson, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Cambridge City, 1952 (Box 7)
    - Carmel, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Clinton, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Columbus, 1951-1955 (Box 7)
    - Covington, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Crawfordsville, 1951-1953 (Box 7)
    - Culver, 1952 (Box 7)
    - Delphi, 1951-1954 (Box 7)
    - Edgewood, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Elkhart, 1951-1953 (Box 7)
    - Fort Wayne, 1950-1956 (Box 7)
    - Frankfort, 1955 (Box 7)
    - Franklin, 1952 (Box 7)
    - Gary, 1953-1955 (Box 7)
    - Goshen, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Greencastle, 1951-1953 (Box 7)
    - Greensburg, 1952-1955 (Box 7)
    - Greenfield, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Hagerstown, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Huntington, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
    - Indianapolis, 1950-1956 (Box 7)
    - Knightstown, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Kokomo, 1950-1953 (Box 7)
    - LaGrange, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Liberty, 1951; 1953 (Box 7)
    - Logansport, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Lynn, 1951; 1952 (Box 7)
    - Madison, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Marion, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Martinsville, 1948-1954 (Box 7)
    - Mishawaka, 1950-1951 (Box 7)
    - Milton, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Monticello, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
    - New Albany, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
    - New Castle, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Peru, 1951; 1952 (Box 7)
    - Plymouth, 1950 (Box 7)
    - Richmond, 1951-1953 (Box 7)
    - Rockville, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Rochester, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
    - Rushville, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Shelbyville, 1951 (Box 7)
    - South Bend, 1951-1953 (Box 7)
    - Sullivan, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Terre Haute, 1952 (Box 7)
    - Tipton, 1952 (Box 7)
    - Valparaiso, 1950; 1951 (Box 7)
    - Vincennes, 1952 (Box 7)
    - Wabash, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
    - Warsaw, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Washington, 1952 (Box 7)
    - West Lafayette, 1950 (Box 7)
    - Winchester (Box 7)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 7)
      - publicity, 1947 (Box 7)
    - Worthington, 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - Leader files, 1947-1953; undated
    - General, ca. 1947 (Box 7)
    - Aeschylus: (Box 7)
      - House of Atreus, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
      - Prometheus Bound; and The Book of Job, ca. 1950 (Box 7)
    - Aristophanes: Lysistrata, Birds, Clouds, ca. 1947 (Box 7)
    - Aristotle: (Box 7)
      - Ethics (Box 7)
        - year one, ca. 1947 (Box 7)
        - year two, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
      - On Interpretation, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
      - Poetics, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
      - Politics (Box 7)
        - Book I, ca. 1947 (Box 7)
        - Book III-IV, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
    - Aurelius, Marcus:Meditations, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
    - Calvin: Institutes of the Christian Religion, undated (Box 7)
    - Cervantes: Don Quixote, 1947-1951; undated (Box 7)
    - Darwin: Origin of Species, 1951 (Box 7)
    - Declaration of Independence and Passages from the Old Testament, ca. 1944-1948 (Box 7)
    - The Federalist Papers and the U.S. Constitution, ca. 1950 (Box 7)
    - Freud: The Origin of Development and Psychoanalysis, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
    - Gibbon: The Decline and Fall of the Roman Empire, ca. 1950 (Box 7)
    - Hobbes: Leviathan, 1948 (Box 7)
    - Homer: The Odyssey, ca. 1948-1958 (Box 7)
    - Herodotus: History, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
    - Kant: Fundamental Principles of Metaphysics and Morals, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
    - Lucian: Selections, 1946-1949 (Box 7)
    - Lucretius: De Rerum Natura, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
      (On the Nature of Things)
    - Locke: Of Civil Government, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
      (2nd essay)
    - Machiavelli: The Prince, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
    - Marx: The Communist Manifesto, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
    - Mill: (Box 7)
      - On Liberty, ca. 1950 (Box 7)
      - Representative Government, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
    - Milton: (Box 7)
      - Areopagitica, 1947-1950 (Box 7)
      - Paradise Lost, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
    - Plato: (Box 7)
      - Apology and Crito, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
      - Meno, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
      - Republic I-II, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
      - Symposium or The Banquet, 1949 (Box 7)
    - Plutarch: Lycurgus and Numa, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
    - Rousseau: (Box 7)
      - Discourse on Inequality, 1949 (Box 7)
      - The Social Contract Books I-II, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
        (Contains the Confessions)
    - St. Augustine: Confessions, ca. 1948 (Box 7)
    - St. Thomas Aquinas: (Box 7)
      - De Magistro, 1949 (Box 7)
      - Treatise on Law, ca. 1947-1953 (Box 7)
    - Shakespeare: (Box 7)
      - Hamlet, ca. 1948-1951 (Box 7)
      - Macbeth, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
    - Smith: The Wealth of Nations, 1948 (Box 7)
    - Spinoza, undated (Box 7)
    - Swift: Gulliver's Travels, ca. 1950 (Box 7)
    - Tawny: Religion and the Rise of Capitalism, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
    - Thoreau: Civil Disobedience, ca. 1950 (Box 7)
    - Thucydides: History, ca. 1947-1953 (Box 7)
    - Voltaire: Candide, ca. 1949 (Box 7)
  - Subject files
    - Awards and clippings, 1969-1983 (Box 7)
    - Bibliographies, 1953; undated (Box 7)
    - Campus Club, 1956 (Box 7)
    - Cloud, Joseph D., 1981 (Box 7)
    - Drafts and draft commentary, 1958; 1983 (Box 7)
    - Hershey Library, 1951-1971; undated (Box 8)
    - Historic Madison and Southern Indiana river trails, 1971-1981 (Box 8)
    - Humphrey campaign (Box 8)
      - April – July, 1968 (Box 8)
      - August – October, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Recommendations (Box 8)
      - A-R, 1951-1983 (Box 8)
      - S-Z, 1951-1981 (Box 8)